ANDRÉS MAURICIO TRIANA REINA

SYSTEMS ENGINEER

+(57) 3108669185



andrestrianareina@outlook.com (>>



@andresmtr



andresmtr.github.io/Andres_Triana_HV/

in/andres-mauricio-triana-reina



SKILLS AND TOOLS

OFFICE

EXCEL WORD

POWER POINT

DATA COLLECTION

GOOGLE FORMS
KOBOTOOLBOX

CODING

JUPYTER NOTEBOOK VISUAL STUDIO CODE GOOGLE COLABORATORY

DATA ANALYTICS AND VISUALIZATION

PYTHON
PANDAS
NUMPY
SEABORN
MATPLOTLIB
PLOTLY
CHART JS
SQL
DATA STUDIO

WEB DEVELOPMENT

HTML CSS BOOTSTRAP JAVASCRIPT PYTHON DJANGO SQL

PROJECT MANAGEMENT

SLACK
TRELLO
MICROSOFT TEAMS

SOFT SKILLS

PROBLEM SOLVING CRITICAL THINKING COMMUNICATION TEAMWORK CREATIVITY

LANGUAGES

SPANISH - NATIVE ENGLISH - B2

PROFILE

Systems engineer with extensive experience in positions such as manage database, evaluation and monitoring, construction of management reports and progress indicators, using Python and Excel for extraction, debugg, analysis, visualization of data and information. Strengths to interpret, analyze and diagnose process advances, well to design and implement operational plans oriented timely decision making.

EXPERIENCE

(2021 - currently employed)

IMMAP

Data Analyst Expert

Compile, debug, process and analytics information from different sources primary and secondary, using new technologies about processing and analysis of data, artificial intelligence, programming languages and data mining to improve the quality of information on the products.

(2018 - 2021)

IOM - INTERNATIONAL ORGANIZATION FOR MIGRATION

Professional system information

Manage databases and update reports indicators, guaranteeing quality and consistency on the information, supporting consolidation of information for internal and external reports.

(2017 - 2018)

ASOCIACIÓN COLOMBIANA DE DISTRIBUIDORES PELÍCULAS CINEMATOGRÁFICAS

Manage databases - Cadbox

Manage databases of sell movie tickets in Colombia and update the information in the app CADBOX. In addition, manage user in the system and create reports to the associates

(2013 - 2017) FUPAD/FUCOLDE

Analyst as evaluation and monitoring

Manage, creation and depuration of databases with the purpose to build information, reports and indicators.

EDUCATION

(2017 - 2020)

UNAD - UNIVERSIDAD NACIONAL ABIERTA Y A DISTANCIA.

Systems engineer

(2014 - 2016)

SENA - SERVICIO NACIONAL DE APRENDIZAJE

Technology in analysis and development of information systems

COURSES/CERTIFICATIONS

Comprehensive SQL Bootcamp : Beginner to Advanced - Udemy SQL course - Sololearn

Interactive Python Dashboards with Plotly and Dash - Udemy Python for Data Sciences and machine learning Bootcamp - Udemy

Big Data Analytics: Opportunities, Challenges and the future - Future Learn

Google Curso de introducción al desarrollo web: HTML y CSS - Google activate

Python course - Sololearn